Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Every year, the Wizard King awards stars to Magic Knight squads for their performance, with each team vying to earn the most.
The squad's achievements, along with the total number of stars they've collected during that year, are announced to the public at an annual event known as the Star Festival.
However, during what should have been a peaceful celebratory evening, Captain Yami and Captain Jack were locked in a dramatic confrontation, the pretense of which was entirely trivial.
Now let's see here.
After their battle reached an unexpected conclusion, the two captains and their squad members made their way back to the Star Festival ground.
Ah!
We'll be right back.
いつかのページ書き殴った
言い訳ばかり探している
毎日にさよなら告げるよ
走り出す列車に飛び乗った
小さくては見えないけど
大丈夫さ
そんな気がするんだ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
I know that magic
She's the Blue Rose Knight's captain
Uh,Shar,whatcha doing there?
Call me Captain,Soul
Okay,Shar
Come along,You said
were you intending to use me
as some sort of arm decoration
and it came as a command
not a request
House Bammleton
Ha!
I hail from the house Roselay
Did you approach so boldly
just because I am a woman?
You are not superior to me
not in the slightest
That jerk
I still can't figure out where we ended up
Yeah,and whose fault is that,Noelle?
I can't believe how many people there are here
You can hold my hand so you don't get lost
What?
Well then
Why aren't you using your magic
to dispel my briars?
Oh,Yeah
That's our amazing leader
Shar for ya
Call me Captain,Soul
You got it,Shar
Wait,No,Somebody stop her
She's gonna kill him
What happened?
Did you see him?
Nah,Just some drunk guy dancing naked
It's not fit for royal eyes
Hey,Wait a minute
Hi there
I know you
The runt
From the other ceremony
Who you calling a runt?
Sorry,but that's what you are
Finding you some kind of giant
Huh?
The little bug is talking like he wants to get squished
Please don't hurt me
Aaah!
Whatever,Back to Shar
Call me Captain
Got it,Shar
Anyway I found you a super fabulous dress
I don't see what's wrong with the one I'm wearing
It'll look great on you
Come on
Wait,Soul
I really don't need it
Aaw,Don't be such a stiff
Wow,Your skin is so pale and beautiful,Shar
It's as smooth as marble,too
Would you stop that?
Aaw,Hoo,HoYou
melons
Alcohol always tastes better when you drink it at a festival
Yeah
There's something special about the food too
You can't get that flavor anywhere else
Yikes,There are way too many people here
Hm
Hey it was pretty good
how i miss marie huh why is this apple extra yummy because we're at a festival
oh or maybe it's because i'm with you festivals always get me way fired up
i'm feeling real manly now i know right want to spar with me a little bit thanks but no thanks
of priceless memories in the book of my life i keep striking out man i must be off my game huh
i smell exquisite beauty nearby gotta go how rude there's plenty of beauty right over here
he sure got some nerve anyway i wonder what could be taking captain yanni so long
i mean you're always gorgeous in your helmet too but this is something else she's divine oh fate
thank you for blessing me i'm in the presence of an angel no the goddess whoa she's really beautiful
oh compose yourselves at once this is not a show huh only the blue rose knights are allowed to get
all goo goo eyed over char's beauty you understand me what that's hardly the issue i just can't risk
letting the other captains see me looking like this especially him what's all the racket over here
you must be partying hard eh good to see you're still with us kid hey don't laugh about that i could
have been seriously hurt you know why don't be such a baby it's not like it killed you
oh no yum he's here why is it him of all people huh you're like stupid hot char no i can't lose my
composure in front of soul calm down charlotte don't panic besides in this outfit he may not even
recognize me huh princess prickly what's with that get up you look like a damn doll deep breaths you
mustn't let him get to you forget my clothing take a look at yours mostly the bottom half are those
undergarments well if it isn't the shabbiest stinkiest man of the whole disgusting bunch
the captain of the black bulls jeez what she's so worked up about think your squad might need a
talking to rosie shut up and keep your hairy naked man legs away from our captain soul that's quite enough
good i finally found you what are you up to captain let's go get a drink shall we
oh vanessa who is this woman and why do i suddenly feel like i have to defeat her at all costs
you don't like the blue rose captain who is she yami seems to be rather chummy with her
is she a member of the black bulls i'm so jealous a lousy black bull like you has no right to glare at
our illustrious leader what i wasn't glaring and i'm certainly not lousy you and your pals wouldn't
stand a chance against her never in a million billion years ain't nice insult real original
i can't take this kind of harassment from a blue rose that's it i need to find a way to defend the
captain's honor enough chit chat time for us to duel that's absurd the ceremony is about to begin soul
stay focused say what char's gonna destroy you for sure we accept your challenge good luck you two
so what'll it be then i should say i'm stronger now than i've ever been before so i won't go down
easily you fool if you knew me you would realize how preposterous you sound i am the captain of the
blue rose knights captain this is about to get really bad shouldn't we stop them no now now ladies if i could
just interject here we're at a festival so let's settle this amicably of course a man would say that
the only thing you could win is a flirting contest ouch in that case let me offer you a suggestion the
perfect battle for two beauties on such a festive evening a dress up showdown
oh that would be ridiculous what's wrong are you scared you're gonna lose of course she's not you
could put char in a burlap sack and she'd still rock it
it sounds like they're all having a good time well good for them they don't appear to be causing any
trouble so it's fine let's make our way to the ceremony we mustn't be late i agree it's a big
night so i'm a little nervous there's no need for us to be nervous we're sure to take the top spot right
but the black bulls have been doing such a great job lately i'm kind of worried they'll surprise us
indeed they may have improved a bit no they definitely have asta in particular has done incredible
things this year it can't be that's impossible they are the black bulls after all they've always been
clowns and ruffians the golden dawn need not concern ourselves with them right do you know you're asking
if i think we'll be outdone by the black bulls the lowest of the low not a chance first up it's the
lovely captain of the blue rose knight charlotte roselay and she'll be dressed up as
oh a sexy witch i'm spellbound i knew if we copied that loser's outfit it would be obvious how much more
elegant and classy char is the choice is crystal clear char's the winner hands down huh naturally
i could never lose to a weakling like her and call me captain
i hate this why do i have to wear these humiliating clothes please yami avert your eyes although since
he's here you might as well look if i resemble that woman who's so friendly with him perhaps
he'll be inclined to become that friendly with me as well but it's embarrassing don't look please i can't
bear it that blue rose lady looks pretty good as a witch doesn't she yeah not that bad be still my
heart next up let's hear it for the black bulls member vanessa and oteca and her costume is oh my i
wasn't expecting a nun talk about a blessing she doesn't know the first thing about men they love to
have their expectations turned upside down this modest look is a complete 180 for a gal who tends to
let it all hang out i pray that you all will lead safe and fulfilling lives
whoa check her out i've never seen vanessa look this good she cleans up nice
okay fellas now send your magic power to the lovely lady of your choosing obviously the winner needs to be
charlotte the witch no way the nun's hotter this is the toughest choice ever and polls are closed
let's see which one of them got more love it's too close to college looks like we have a tie
oh come on it doesn't make a difference to me all that just a tie i've shamed house roselay
still i wonder what yami thought about the whole thing perhaps he sees me differently now if that's
true i would consider this ordeal to have been worthwhile yeah right as if char would ever tie let's
settle this for real i'm ready when you are okay then our next battle will be a swimsuit competition
feel free to change on stage if you don't mind tang me up huh i mean sorry anyone who agrees with
him will meet the same fate step right up folks and quench your thirst with a clover premium select
it's a rich and mellow brew with a hint of fruity flavor made right here in clover kingdom with only
the finest ingredients captain yami you like a girl who knows how to drink right huh where'd that come
from yeah so we can drink together it's good bonding but why oh i see this one's in the bag
i challenge you to a drinking contest spare me your silly games are getting old i'm done
it's almost time for the star ceremony don't worry char i've got you all set up and taken care of over
here now give that catty witch a taste of her own medicine and drink her under the table
these are the rules whoever can consume the most beer in the next hour will be victorious
we'll be drinking clover premium select it's a local treasure however there's no chugging
it's just not a good look and it's polite to the brewer to drink slowly and taste it how is this
happening and now let the drinking begin that's it sure sure who's boss i don't really know what's
going on but i'm rooting for you vanessa she definitely knows how to hold her alcohol this won't be an
easy fight for me you've got your life cut off of you now little miss man oh my it seems she's
already three sheets to the wind nerve challenging me in that state i can keep knocking these things back
for days wow strong stuff no she's just a lightweight oh but she's so adorable when she's all tipsy
what the hell are these broads doing i'm fighting an impossible battle just for yami there must be
something wrong with me no curse a curse on house rose lay on your daughter's 18th birthday a terrible
magic will be awakened and you'll be helpless to stop it it will swallow up every one of you and
and trap you within a cage of time oh charlotte what a dreadful thing this is if only when you
away to lift this unspeakable curse please don't cry mother father i'll just get strong really strong
and then someday i can break it myself she's had another fine showing yeah she may be a newcomer but
she's obviously really powerful not to mention drop dead gorgeous
miss charlotte i'd be honored to make you my bride no marry me instead please
anyone who can't defeat me cannot hope to handle my curse
every man is the same all bark and no bite
the only person who can rescue me is me
what the hell it's the curse on house rosely
there's no hope it's too strong
i can't stop it at this rate the village damn it so pitiful so shameful
forgive me father
you really made a mess of things huh
Huh. Made me spill the pasta I was eating all over the place.
Yamizuka Hiro. How can I let him see me in this sorry state? I am defeated.
I'm not a fan of chicks who prance into battle acting all smug when they have no reason to be.
I prefer women who are strong.
But you can lean on someone else every once in a while.
You know how you can find lots of other strong people to lean on? By joining the Magic Knights.
Having my heart stolen by a man. That was the secret to ending my curse.
Hey, who went away? Lucky break.
And of all the men in the world, it had to be this stubborn brute.
You don't drink, right? Didn't I tell you a long time ago it's not good to force yourself?
Cheering mugs is practically kissing.
The contest is a draw!
Good job, Shar! Even if it was just a tie!
Yeah, and you did great too, Vanessa!
Well, that sure turned out to be a whole lot of nothing, didn't it?
The star ceremony is getting ready to start!
All the captains are going to be there!
Even the new captains of the Crimson Lion Kings and the Purple Orcas!
I wonder what they're like!
Uh...
All of them?
Uh-oh.
Damn it, we're late.
Nah, the wait for me.
The star ceremony.
And I'm going to be here.
I'm going to be here.
Um, I'm still here.
Let's see.
Hey.
Just a melody
I love
The promise of my soul
I'll make it true
My soul, my days
This world, let go
Let go
I'll make it true
My soul, my days
I'll see you next time.
Oh, yeah, till death do us fart!
Number three is Samurai Charlotte.
Cut me to bits!
Number four, meet Professor Charlotte.
Instruct me in the ways of love!
Number five is Policewoman Charlotte.
Go on, cuff me!
Costume six, Ninja Charlotte.
Oh, sneak up on me anytime!
I don't have time for this.
Poof!
I thought there were seven.
It's finally time to reveal the Magic Knight standings.
Black Bulls may have a decent chance this year.
I know because I've been watching my friends
without blinking from a very close distance.
Black Clover, page 70.
Two new stars.
We'll be friends forever.